sneakerwatch.com 2016-05-01

# Privacy Policy | SneakerWatch.com // SneakerWatch

Thank you for visiting SneakerWatch.com (the “Site”), a Hot In Here, INC (“SNW”) Website.  We take your privacy seriously, and have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy gathered on the Site.  Keep reading to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of your personal information.  
 **  
Information We Collect**

This Site collects information from you in a variety of ways, including User Registration, contests, products, online forums and user polls. Thus in visiting this Site we may collect some personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.    
We also collect certain non-personal information when you visit this Site, such certain types of Web site usage information. For example, we may collect the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view, or other similar information.  When analyzed, Web site usage information helps us determine how visitors arrive at the Site, what type of content is most popular, and what type of visitors are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising.

 **How We Use Your Information**

We use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, or to contact you about your account with us.  We also use this information to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We reserve the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of SNW (or its parents, subsidiaries or affiliates), the Site or a transfer of all or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.  We also reserve the right to permit any parents, subsidiaries and affiliates to use your information, although such parties shall be subject to the restrictions under this Privacy Policy.  
We use the non personal information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience.  Examples include hosting our web servers, analyzing Site Usage, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service.  
Moreover, if you submit to SNW and/or Site comments, photographs, videos, music, text or other content, it may be published online or offline (including on-air, on a CD or DVD, through wireless distribution, and transmission of soft copies, or any other media or format currently existing or hereafter developed), and we may publish your name, voice, likeness and other personal information in connection with publishing the content or a portion of the content, and we may use the content and any excerpt from the content in connection with advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities.  Please also see our Terms of Use, which governs any content you submit through the Site. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you the personal information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Links and Advertisements**

We expect our sponsors, partners and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users.  However, when you are on the Site you may be directed to other sites that are operated and controlled by third parties that are beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Site onto a different Web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the Site's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Web sites may independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a web site that is linked from our Site, you should consult that Web site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

 **Cookies and Other Technical Information**

Personal information collected by this Site can be linked to other data stored in Cookies on your computer.  ”Cookies" are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data).  Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser).  We send Cookies to your computer primarily to enhance your online experience

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of Cookies as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other sites.  Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information.  However, certain areas of the Site can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content.   
As mentioned above, we sometimes use third party content providers and advertisers. These third-parties may use Cookies or similar devices to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements.  You should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party advertiser site to determine how you may be affected by the third parties’ use of Cookies.  
 **  
User Comments**

This Site may allow users to make comments on the site (“User Comments”). If you post User Comments containing personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.  We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public on a comment board.  Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy.  Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas.  Any User Comments are also subject to our Terms of Use.

 **Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy.  If we make material changes in the way we treat your personal information, we will place a notice to that effect on this Site.  We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at: [info@sneakerwatch.com](mailto:info@sneakerwatch.com)
